{
    "subject": "resource/Offenbach_am_Main",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Germany",
    "human_readable": "Offenbach am Main is located in Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9187877178192139,
            "question": "Where is Offenbach am Main located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8312093615531921,
            "question": "What is the geographic location of Offenbach am Main?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8220610618591309,
            "question": "What country is Offenbach am Main in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7224544286727905,
            "question": "Is Offenbach am Main a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5765857100486755,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Offenbach am Main?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.530222475528717,
            "question": "Is Offenbach am Main a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42881152033805847,
            "question": "What language is primarily spoken in Offenbach am Main?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38933879137039185,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Offenbach am Main?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31052976846694946,
            "question": "Does Offenbach am Main have a rich history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12130646407604218,
            "question": "Can you name any cities in Germany?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Offenbach am Main is located in Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3989_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Offenbach am Main have a rich history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3989_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Offenbach am Main?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3989_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language is primarily spoken in Offenbach am Main?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3989_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3989_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents clearly indicate that Offenbach am Main is located in Germany, Hesse. Therefore, the statement \"Offenbach am Main is located in Germany\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}